<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hello World on Triboar Guildhall — Westmarches D&amp;D Community</title><link>https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/</link><description>Recent content in Hello World on Triboar Guildhall — Westmarches D&amp;D Community</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Forgotten Realms</title><link>https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/setting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/setting/</guid><description>A World Alive with Stories The Realms are designed for breadth. Players can step into a bustling frontier town, explore the ruins of lost empires, or set sail across perilous seas. Each region offers a unique flavor, from the mercantile cities of the Sword Coast to the shadowy depths of the Underdark.
Why the Forgotten Realms? Familiar yet flexible: The Realms provide a shared foundation that&amp;rsquo;s easy to step into, while still leaving room for new tales.</description></item><item><title>Triboar Guildhall Charter</title><link>https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/charter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/charter/</guid><description>Purpose The Triboar Guildhall exists to bring together storytellers, writers, and roleplayers who want to explore the Forgotten Realms through collaborative, play-by-post adventures. Our goal is to create a space where creativity thrives, stories unfold at their own pace, and everyone feels welcome at the table.
Core Values Collaboration – Storytelling here is shared. Every character matters, every post builds on the last.
Respect – We honor each other&amp;rsquo;s time, contributions, and creative choices.</description></item><item><title>Triboar Guildhall FAQ</title><link>https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/faq/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adamhstewart.github.io/triboar-site/faq/</guid><description>What is Triboar Guildhall? Triboar Guildhall is a play-by-post (PbP) community for tabletop roleplaying games, primarily set in the Forgotten Realms. We&amp;rsquo;re writers, storytellers, and adventurers who build shared stories one post at a time.
What is play-by-post? Play-by-post (PbP) means the game unfolds through written posts in Discord instead of live voice sessions. Each player writes their character&amp;rsquo;s actions, thoughts, and dialogue; the Dungeon Master (DM) responds with narration, NPCs, and the unfolding story.</description></item></channel></rss>